<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <string name="app_name">SubMission1</string>
    <string name="title_tv">TV SHOW</string>
    <string name="title_film">FILM</string>

    <string name="change_lang">Change language</string>


    //tv show
    <array name="show_poster">
        <item>@drawable/poster_arrow</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_doom_patrol</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon_ball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_family_guy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_flash</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_god</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_gotham</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_grey_anatomy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hanna</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_iron_fist</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_naruto_shipudden</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_ncis</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_riverdale</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_shameless</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_supergirl</item>
    </array>

    <array name="judul_show">
        <item>Arrow</item>
        <item>Doom Patrol</item>
        <item>Poster Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Family Guy</item>
        <item>Flash</item>
        <item>Gotham</item>
        <item>Grey_Anatomy</item>
        <item>Hanna</item>
        <item>Iron First</item>
        <item>Naruto Shipudden</item>
        <item>NCIS</item>
        <item>Riverdale</item>
        <item>Shameless</item>
        <item>Supergirl</item>
    </array>

    <array name="deskripsi_show">
        <item>Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht
            is lost at sea. He returns five years later a changed man, determined to clean up the
            city as a hooded vigilante armed with a bow.</item>

        <item>The Doom Patrol’s members each suffered horrible accidents that gave them superhuman
            abilities — but also left them scarred and disfigured. Traumatized and downtrodden,
            the team found purpose through The Chief, who brought them together to investigate
            the weirdest phenomena in existence — and to protect Earth from what they find.</item>

        <item>Long ago in the mountains, a fighting master known as Gohan discovered a
            strange boy whom he named Goku. Gohan raised him and trained Goku in martial arts
            until he died. The young and very strong boy was on his own, but easily managed. Then
            one day, Goku met a teenage girl named Bulma, whose search for the dragon balls brought
            her to Goku\'s home. Together, they set off to find all seven dragon balls in an
            adventure that would change Goku\'s life forever. See how Goku met his life long friends
            Bulma, Yamcha, Krillin, Master Roshi and more. And see his adventures as a boy, all
            leading up to Dragonball Z and later Dragonball GT.</item>

        <item>Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin\' Sweet animated series featuring
            the adventures of the dysfunctional Griffin family. Bumbling Peter and long-suffering
            Lois have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but sadistic baby bent on killing his mother
            and taking over the world), Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl in town)
            and Chris (the middle kid, he\'s not very bright but has a passion for movies). The
            final member of the family is Brian - a talking dog and much more than a pet, he keeps
            Stewie in check whilst sipping Martinis and sorting through his own life issues.</item>

        <item>After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is
            struck by lightning and falls into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of
            super speed, granting him the ability to move through Central City like an unseen
            guardian angel. Though initially excited by his newfound powers, Barry is shocked to
            discover he is not the only "meta-human" who was created in the wake of the accelerator
            explosion -- and not everyone is using their new powers for good. Barry partners with
            S.T.A.R. Labs and dedicates his life to protect the innocent. For now, only a few
            close friends and associates know that Barry is literally the fastest man alive, but it
            won\'t be long before the world learns what Barry Allen has become...The Flash.</item>

        <item>Everyone knows the name Commissioner Gordon. He is one of the crime world\'s greatest
            foes, a man whose reputation is synonymous with law and order. But what is known of
            Gordon\'s story and his rise from rookie detective to Police Commissioner? What did
            it take to navigate the multiple layers of corruption that secretly ruled Gotham
            City, the spawning ground of the world\'s most iconic villains? And what
            circumstances created them – the larger-than-life personas who would become Catwoman,
            The Penguin, The Riddler, Two-Face and The Joker?</item>

        <item>Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattle\’s Grey
            Sloan Memorial Hospital.</item>

        <item>This thriller and coming-of-age drama follows the journey of an extraordinary young
            girl as she evades the relentless pursuit of an off-book CIA agent and tries to unearth
            the truth behind who she is. Based on the 2011 Joe Wright film.</item>

        <item>Danny Rand resurfaces 15 years after being presumed dead. Now, with the power of the
            Iron Fist, he seeks to reclaim his past and fulfill his destiny.t</item>

        <item>Naruto Shippuuden is the continuation of the original animated TV series Naruto.
            The story revolves around an older and slightly more matured Uzumaki Naruto and his
            quest to save his friend Uchiha Sasuke from the grips of the snake-like Shinobi,
            Orochimaru. After 2 and a half years Naruto finally returns to his village of Konoha,
            and sets about putting his ambitions to work, though it will not be easy, as He has
            amassed a few (more dangerous) enemies, in the likes of the shinobi organization;
            Akatsuki.</item>

        <item>From murder and espionage to terrorism and stolen submarines, a team of special
            agents investigates any crime that has a shred of evidence connected to Navy and Marine
            Corps personnel, regardless of rank or position.</item>

        <item>Set in the present, the series offers a bold, subversive take on Archie, Betty,
            Veronica and their friends, exploring the surreality of small-town life, the darkness
            and weirdness bubbling beneath Riverdale’s wholesome facade.</item>

        <item>Chicagoan Frank Gallagher is the proud single dad of six smart, industrious,
            independent kids, who without him would be... perhaps better off. When Frank\'s not at t
            he bar spending what little money they have, he\'s passed out on the floor. But the kids
            have found ways to grow up in spite of him. They may not be like any family you know,
            but they make no apologies for being exactly who they are.</item>

        <item>Twenty-four-year-old Kara Zor-El, who was taken in by the Danvers family when she was
            13 after being sent away from Krypton, must learn to embrace her powers after
            previously hiding them. The Danvers teach her to be careful with her powers, until she
            has to reveal them during an unexpected disaster,
            setting her on her journey of heroism.</item>
    </array>


    /film
    <array name="movie_poster">
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hunterkiller</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="movie_judul">
        <item>Aquaman</item>

        <item>A Star is Born</item>

        <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>

        <item>Bird Box</item>

        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>

        <item>Bumblebee</item>

        <item>Creed II</item>

        <item>Deadpool 2</item>

        <item>Hunter Killer</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="movie_deskripsi">
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth,
            Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. </item>

        <item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers — and falls in love with — struggling
            artist Ally.</item>

        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from
            threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the
            cosmic shadows: Thanos.</item>

        <item>Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide,
            a survivor and her two children make a desperate bid to reach safety.</item>

        <item>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and
            bass guitarist John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock \'n\'
            roll band Queen in 1970.</item>

        <item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a
            small Californian beach town.</item>

        <item>Between personal obligations and training for his next big
            fight against an opponent with ties to his family\'s past, Adonis Creed
            is up against the challenge of his life.</item>

        <item>Wisecracking mercenary Deadpool battles the evil and powerful Cable
            and other bad guys to save a boy\'s life.</item>


        <item>Captain Glass of the USS Arkansas discovers that a coup d\'état is taking
            place in Russia, so he and his crew join an elite group working on the ground to
            prevent a war.</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>
